别看  别看
Don't look. Don't look.
别  等等
Wait wait wait wait.
妈
Ma...
快点
Come on!
把她拉开  把她拉开
Pull her away, pull her away!
我们到处跑  一直在树林子里找她
We've been out. We've been combing these woods looking for her
结果她一直在那谷仓里
and she was in there all along?
-你们一早就知道了  -别烦我们
- You knew. - Leave us alone.
-肖恩  消停点吧  -别碰我
- Hey, Shane, just stop, man. - Get your hands off me.
-我...  -你们早知道  还瞒着我们
- I... - You knew and you kept it from us.
-我不知道  -一派胡言
- I didn't know. - That's bullshit.
-你们肯定都知道  -我们不知道
- I think y'all knew. - We didn't know!
-她为什么会在那儿  -你们...
- Why was she there?! - Your--
奥蒂斯把这些人关在谷仓里的
Otis put those people in the barn.
也许他死前发现了她所以把她关那儿了
Maybe he found her and put her in there before he was killed.
你觉得我会相信这一套吗
You expect me to believe that?
-你把我当白痴吗  -肖恩  别这样
- Do I look like an idiot? - Shane, hey hey hey.
-我才不管你相不相信  -大家都冷静
- I don't care what you believe! - Everybody just calm down.
-让他滚出我的地盘  -都别激动
- Get him off my land! - Please. No.
-让我告开导你几句  -别碰他
- Let me tell you something. - Hey. Don't touch him!
你折腾够了没
Haven't you done enough?
我说真的  离开我的地方
I mean it-- off my land.
你这是干嘛
what are you doing?
你到底想干嘛
Hey, what are you doing?
达里尔为了找她差点没命  瑞克
Daryl almost died looking for her, Rick.
我们谁都有可能送命  我告诉你
Any one of us could have. I'm gonna tell you right now--
那个老混蛋  他早就知道
That son of a bitch, he knew.
他不知道  他不是这种人
He didn't know. He's not like that.
-是他收留了我们  -是他让我们身处险境
- He opened his home to us. - He put us all endanger.
伙计  他藏了一谷仓行尸
Man, he kept a barn full of walkers.
所以你就发起暴动
So you just start an insurrection,
分发枪支  杀了他的家人吗
hand out guns and massacre his family?
他那一家早都死了  瑞克
His family's dead, Rick.
可是他不那么认为
Well, he doesn't believe that.
他认为你残忍地杀了他们
He thinks you just murdered them in cold blood.
不  伙计  我才不管他怎么想
No, man, I don't care what he thinks.
我当时正在处理这事  老兄
I was handling it, brother.
是我在处理的  你就只会...
I was handling it and you just--
你只会让我们去树林里找那小女孩
You had us out in those woods looking for a little girl
可我们谁都明白她早已经死了
that every single one of us knew was dead!
你就做了这点事  瑞克
That's what you did. Rick.
你跟那老头一样只会妄想
you're just as delusional as that guy.
你在处理这事  是吧
You handling it, huh?
《行尸走肉》
我必须得问问
I have to ask you--
你知道她在谷仓里吗
Did you know she was in the barn?
其实  也许这才是最好的结局
You know, maybe in some weird way this is for the best.
至少大家知道后  就可以继续前行
At least we know and now we can move on.
-前行  -对  就是说...
- Move on? - Yeah, it's just like...
找到她  对大家来说
It meant so much to everyone--
都很重要
finding her, you know?
-然后  -这么说  你们准备继续前进了
- And then-- - so now you'll just move on?
如果可以的话
If we can.
我是说  我们已经失去过其他人
I mean, we've lost others.
这次  这次是索菲亚
This is-- this is Sophia.
在整个队伍里
The whole group--
她是与众不同的
This one was different.
那么  现在要怎么办呢
So what happens now?
我们要葬了她
We bury her...
还有你的继母和哥哥
with your stepmom and your stepbrother.
然后呢
And then?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我以为我最后会找到她的
I thought I'd find her.
我们都这么以为
We all did.
我是指  我
I mean, me...
是我会找到她
That I'd be the one.
就像她在某处躲猫猫
Like maybe she was hiding somewhere
藏在洞里或者树后面
in a cave or a tree.
她会很安全
She'd be safe
然后我会找到她  带她回来
and I'd find her and bring her back.
他做得对
He did the right thing,
把她射杀
shooting her like that.
要是我  我也会这么做
I would've done it, too.
戴尔
Dale?
-怎么了  -你带卡尔到屋子里去行吗
- Yeah? - Could you take Carl up to the house?
你好好休息
I want you to rest.
好的
Okay.
你帽子忘拿了
Hey, you dropped that.
现在开始埋吗
You want us to start burying?
我们得做个礼拜仪式
We need a service.
卡萝尔会希望我们做的
Carol would want that.
对  我们都这么想的
Yeah, we all want that.
我们给索菲亚挖个坟墓吧
Let's-- let's dig a grave for Sophia,
还有安妮特和沙恩
and Annette and Shawn,
就在那边的树底下
uh, over by those trees.
我们还需要一辆卡车把这些尸体运走
And we'll need a truck to move the bodies.
-我去拿钥匙  -不用
- I'll get the keys. - No no.
我去开车
I got the truck.
其他人呢  都土葬的话工作量太大了
And the others? That's a lot of digging.
把我们爱的人土葬了  其他人烧掉
We bury the ones we love and burn the rest.
开始吧
Let's get to work.
赫谢尔怎么说
What did Hershel say?
他说要么让肖恩离开农场
He wants us off the farm,
要么我们都离开这
or Shane at least.
这不算过分
That's not a surprise.
我们之中没再死人已经够幸运的了
We're lucky someone wasn't killed.
刚才那一阵枪声
And all that gunfire--
会把更多的行尸引来的
more walkers could've heard it.
宝贝  怎么了
Baby, what is it?
她一直都在那里面
She was there all the time.
你做了力所能及的事情
And you did everything you could.
对  我知道  我是做了
Yeah, I know. I always do, don't I?
追上她  保护她
Went after her, protected her,
杀死那些行尸  可是她还是被咬了
killed those walkers, but she still got bit.
卡尔也还是中枪了
And Carl still got shot.
大家都听我的  可是我却让他们去树林里
People counting on me and I had 'em chasing
搜寻根本不可能找到的东西
a ghost in a forest.
你有话要说吗  戴尔
Do you got something to say, Dale?
直说吧  老兄
Well, go ahead, man.
道德权威先生  对吧
Mr. Moral authority, huh?
理性发言人
The--the voice of reason.
我问你个问题  老兄  你是做什么的
Let me ask you something, man. What do you do?
你做了什么来保护我们营地的安全
What do you do to keep this camp safe, huh?
你是做什么的  修个破房车
What do you do? What, you fix up an R.V.?
像看小孩一样看着枪
You babysit some guns?
你拿枪指过我对吧
Man, you pointed one at my chest, right?
但是你就是开不了枪  你能吗
But you just-- you couldn't pull that trigger, could you?
如果我真是那么危险  威胁了大家的安全
If I was such a danger, if I was such a threat,
你做了什么来阻止我
what did you do to stop me, huh?
我毁了那个谷仓  我救了卡尔  都是我
I smashed that barn. I saved Carl. That's me.
不是你也不是瑞克  是我
That ain't you. That ain't Rick. That's me.
我告诉你  戴尔
Tell you what, Dale--
下次我需要一根水箱软管的时候
Next time I need a radiator hose...
我会给你打电话的
I'll give you a call, man.
好了
That's it.
他们准备好了
They're ready.
走吧
Come on.
为什么
Why?
因为那是你的女儿
'Cause that's your little girl.
那不是我的女儿
That's not my little girl.
那是别的东西
That's some other thing.
我的索菲亚自己待在树林里
My Sophia was alone in the woods.
我一直在想
All this time I thought...
她并没有哭着入睡
She didn't cry herself to sleep.
她并没有饿肚子
She didn't go hungry.
她并没有寻找回来的路
She didn't try to find her way back.
索菲亚很久以前就死了
Sophia died a long time ago.
-又得出去一趟  -我们算幸运了
- A few more trips. - We got lucky.
如果那个谷仓里行尸更多的话
If that barn had any more,
我们就搞不定了
we could've been overrun.
幸亏肖恩在正确的时间
Good thing Shane did what he did...
-做了该做的事  -你别告诉我这么做是对的
- when he did. - You can't tell me this was right.
那是不对的  那会破坏我们和赫谢尔的关系
It wasn't. It'll cost us with Hershel.
他很伤心  但是他会缓过来的
He's grieving. He'll come around,
我们别无选择
see we had no choice.
我也开枪了  不全是肖恩的责任
Look, I shot too. This wasn't all Shane.
我也不后悔
Look, I got no qualms about it.
后院关着一群行尸
Walkers in my backyard?
无法忍受
Hm-mmm.
我不是埋怨大家当时不应该这么做
I'm not saying that we shouldn't have
但是有必要制造一场恐慌吗
taken care of the problem, but creating a panic?!
再为这件事情争论下去毫无意义  木已成舟
There's no point arguing about it. It's done.
我们什么都做不了
There's nothing we can do about it.
该走了
Better get moving.
等下  停一下
Hey! Hey!
好了
All right!
如果你们的人要走  你也不会留下吗
So if your group leaves, you wouldn't stay?
我真没考虑过这件事
I-- I hadn't really thought about it.
我是说  我不知道
I mean, I-- I didn't know that--
你觉得现在是...
Do-- do you think this is really the time...
-讨论这件事的好时机吗  -我真觉得
- to discuss this, I mean? - Well, I'm not
我们没什么时间了
really feeling like there's a lot of time for anything.
不是的  有的
No no, there-- there is.
时间是有的  我是说  我想
There is. I mean, I-I-- I want--
天呐
Oh my god.
亲爱的  你能听见我说话吗
Sweetie, can you hear me?
-她怎么了  -可能休克了
- What's wrong with her? - She might be in shock.
-赫谢尔哪去了  -我们到处都找不到他
- Where's Hershel? - We can't find him anywhere.
嘿  孩子
Hey, kiddo.
-你继母的东西吗  -他坚信她能被治好
- Your stepmother's things? - He was so sure she'd recover.
一切都保持着他们离开时的样子
They'd just pick up where they left off.
看起来他找到了一位老朋友
Looks like he found an old friend.
那是我祖父的  去世的时候传给了我爸爸
That belonged to my grandfather, gave it to dad when he died.
我还以为赫谢尔不喝酒呢
I didn't take Hershel for a drinker.
他是不喝  我出生那天他就戒了
No, he gave it up on the day I was born.
他甚至在家里禁酒
He didn't even allow liquor in the house.
-镇上有酒吧吗  -有  哈特林家的酒吧
- What's the bar in town? - Hatlin's.
他酗酒那些年  几乎天天就泡在那儿
He practically lived there in his drinking days.
我打赌能在那儿找到他
Betting that's where I'll find him.
我知道怎么走  我带你去吧
Yeah, I've seen the place. I'll take you.
-好的  我去开车  -好
- All right, I'll get the truck. - Okay.
-不行  -这没啥
- N-- no. - It's an easy run.
-像药房那次吗  -嘿  玛姬
- Like the pharmacy? - Hey, Maggie?
我会带他回来的
I'll bring him back.
玛姬  那次不同
Maggie, that was different.
瑞克  你动身之前
Rick? You want to have a
准备告诉我一声吗
conversation about this before you leave?
这么说  你真的要去找他
So you're seriously gonna go after this guy
不管这儿的事了吗
with everything that's going on, huh?
-你要怎样  -他说得对
- What you gonna do? - He's right.
现在不是调头走人的时候
This is not the time to head off, not today.
-你不知道...  -我不跟你争
- You don't know what's have-- - I'm not arguing.
-这是我唯一能做的  我们已经  -已经干嘛了
- It's the least I can do for Hershel after we-- - What?
我们干嘛了
After we what?
卡尔说  换做是他  他也会杀了索菲亚
Carl said he would've shot Sophia himself.
那是你儿子  他变得冷酷了
That's your son. He's getting cold.
他成长的世界充满...
He's growing up in a world with--
他成长的世界需要一个像你这样的父亲
He's growing up in a world where he needs a father like you--
活着  陪着他
around, alive,
而不是跑来跑去帮助每个人
Not running off, solving everybody else's problems.
我想解决的不只是他的问题
It's not just his problem I'm trying to solve.
为了你肚子里的孩子  我们需要赫谢尔
We need Hershel for the baby.
我要去找他
I'm going after him.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
卡萝尔
Carol?
Carol.
嘿嘿嘿
Hey hey hey hey hey.
嘿  你没事儿吧
Hey, are you all right?
快过来
Come here.
你女儿的事  我很遗憾
I want you to know that I'm real sorry for your girl.
谢谢
Thank you.
当我打开谷仓时  我根本不知道
When I opened that barn I had no idea.
如果我...
If I did...
大家都觉得我是个...
Everybody thinks that I'm a...
我只是想保证大家安全
I was just trying to keep everybody safe.
我根本不知道她在里面
I had no idea she was in there.
这儿的日子也不好过了
This place is going to hell.
是啊  我正在努力阻止
Yeah, I'm trying hard to prevent that.
你无能为力
You won't be able to.
没办法  我们当中有人认为
No, there are people in this group
肖恩做的是正确的
who think that what Shane did was justified.
我知道你俩合不来
I know you two can't stand each other,
但他确实做了些正确的事
but he did something that needed to be done.
他很危险
He's dangerous.
是啊  他生性冲动
Yeah, he's a hothead.
不  洛莉  他真的很危险
No, Lori, he's dangerous.
我觉得是他杀了奥蒂斯
I think he killed Otis.
奥蒂斯是被行尸杀的
Otis was killed by walkers.
他知道怎么对付行尸
He knew how to handle walkers.
奥蒂斯有本事把它们抓进仓库去
Otis was the one who was putting them in the barn.
你给我把话说清楚
You need to be really clear with me right now.
-你到底是什么意思  -我认为
- What are you saying? - I believe that--
肖恩牺牲了奥蒂斯
that Shane sacrificed Otis.
我没法证明  但我
I can't prove it, but I-I-I--
我觉得他开枪打了他
I think that he-- I think that he shot him
然后扔下他做诱饵  好让自己脱身
and left him for bait, so that he could get away.
肖恩可能很鲁莽  但他不是杀人犯
Shane may be a hothead, but he's not a murderer.
况且  他怎么会杀一个想帮忙的人呢
And-- and why would he kill somebody who's trying to help?
我不知道  也许他当时走投无路了
I don't know. Maybe he was pinned down.
他说出来了  当着我的面
He said-- he said it. He all but threw it in my face.
我跟你说  我了解他这种人
I'm telling you-- I knew guys like him,
迟早
And sooner or later...
他会再次杀人的
He's gonna kill somebody else.
玛姬说她爱我
Maggie said she loves me.
她不是认真的
She doesn't mean it.
我是说她不可能
I mean she can't.
我的意思是  呃
I mean-- well...
她不开心  或是困惑
She-- she's upset or confused.
也许她觉得...
She's probably feeling, like--
她是个明白人  知道自己心里想什么
I think she's smart enough to know what she's feeling.
不  不
No. No.
不  你知道吗  她想恋爱
No, you know what? She wants to be in love.
所以她需要些东西...去抓住
So she's-- she needs something to-- to, like-- to hold onto.
格伦  大家都看得出来玛姬爱你
Glenn, it's pretty obvious to everyone Maggie loves you,
而且不只是因为你是这世界仅剩的男人
and not just because you're one of the last men standing.
所以有什么问题嘛
So what's the problem?
我没有说爱她
I didn't say it back.
以前从来没女人跟我说这话
I've never had a woman say that to me before
当然  除了我妈
Except my mom, of course,
还有我的姐姐们
And my sisters.
可玛姬不同
But with Maggie, it's different.
我们根本不了解对方
We barely know each other.
她了解我什么
What-- what does she really know about me?
一无所知
Nothing.
几乎是两个陌生人
We're practically strangers.
但我  我不知道怎么处理这件事
But I-- I didn't know what to do with it.
我像个傻瓜似的站在那
I just stood there like a jerk.
这是件好事
Hey. Hey, this is a good thing,
是这个世道正缺少的东西
Something we don't get enough of these days.
享受吧
Enjoy it.
等我们回来了  再回报她
And when we get back, return the favor.
她又去不了哪里
It's not like she's going anywhere.
瑞克
Rick?
我知道洛莉...
I know about Lori,
怀孕的事
Her being pregnant.
-我给她弄的药  -我早知道了
- I got her those pills. - I figured.
抱歉我瞒了你
Hey, I'm sorry I kept it from you.
别这样  你做了自己认为对的事
Don't be. You did what you thought was right.
只是碰巧你错了
It just so happens it wasn't.
她心跳加快  烧起来了
Her heart's racing. She's burning up.
我们需要赫谢尔  他知道怎么做
We need Hershel. He'll know what to do.
-你能帮我照看下卡尔吗  -当然
- Would you look in on carl for me? - Of course.
要搬到这荒郊野外来啊
Moving to the suburbs?
贝丝有点处于紧张性休克状态
Listen, Beth's in some kind of catatonic shock.
-我们需要赫谢尔  -所以呢
- We need Hershel. - Yeah. So what?
所以我要你快速进城一趟
So I need you to run into town real quick
把他和瑞克带回来
And bring him and Rick back.
达里尔
Daryl?
你们女人站着说话不腰疼
Your bitch went window-shopping.
你需要他就自己去带他回来
You want him? Fetch him yourself.
我有别的事要做
I got better things to do.
你怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
别那么自私
Don't you be so selfish.
自私?  听着  奥丽弗(动画片《大力水手》中女主角)
Selfish? Listen to me, olive oyl.
我每一天都出去找那个小姑娘
I was out there looking for that little girl every single day.
挨了一枪还中了一箭
I took a bullet and an arrow in the process.
别跟我说我没有尽心尽力
Don't you tell me about me getting my hands dirty!
你想要找那两个笨蛋  祝你一帆风顺
You want those two idiots? Have a nice ride.
我不会再去找人了
I'm done looking for people.
赫谢尔
Hershel.
谁跟你一起
Who's with you?
格兰
Glenn.
玛姬让他来的吗
Maggie sent him?
他自愿的
He volunteered.
-喝了多少瓶了  -还不够多
- How many have you had? - Not enough.
回家再把这瓶喝完吧
Let's finish this up back at home.
贝丝晕倒了
Beth collapsed,
肯定是受了惊吓  想必你也是
Must be in shock. I think you are too.
玛姬和她在一起吗
Maggie's with her?
是的  但是贝丝需要你
Yeah, but beth needs you.
我能做什么呢
What could I do?
她需要她母亲
She needs her mother.
更确切地说是需要悼念她
or rather to mourn.
几个礼拜前她就该这样了
Like she should've done weeks ago.
现在我明白了
I see that now.
你以前认为有解药
You thought there was a cure.
不要因为一直坚持希望而责怪自己
Can't blame yourself for holding out for hope.
希望
Hope?
当我第一次看到你抱着你儿子
When I first saw you running across my field
穿过田地的时候
With your boy in your arms,
我对他活下来不抱希望
I had little hope he would survive.
但是他活下来了
But he did.
是啊
He did.
尽管我们失去了奥蒂斯
Even though we lost Otis.
你们的人肖恩回来了
Your man Shane made it back
我们救了你儿子
And we saved your boy.
那个奇迹向我证实却有奇迹存在
That was the miracle that proved to me miracles do exist.
却不过是个假象  诱你上钩  然后调包
Only it was a sham, a bait and switch.
我是个傻子  瑞克
I was a fool, Rick,
你们的人都看到了
and you people saw that.
我的女儿们不该如此
My daughters deserve better than that.
我们该怎么办  等他昏倒吗
So what do we do? Just wait for him to pass out?
快走
Just go.
赶紧走
Just go!
我向玛姬保证我会把你安全带回
I promised maggie I'd bring you home safe.
如你向那个小姑娘保证的那样
like you promised that little girl?
那你的计划是什么  喝完那瓶
So what's your plan? Finish that bottle?
喝到死为止  留下你的女儿们孤孤单单
Drink yourself to death and leave your girls alone?
别告诉我
Stop telling me
怎么照顾我的家庭  我的农场
How to care for my family, my farm.
你们这些人就像祸水
You people are like a plague!
我按基督教义行事  给你们安身之处
I do the christian thing, give you shelter,
你们却毁了一切
And you destroy it all!
我们来时世道已经混乱不堪
The world was already in bad shape when we met.
而你却不负责任
And you take no responsibility!
你应该领导他们
You're supposed to be their leader!
我这不是在这里吗
Well, I'm here now, aren't I?
对
Yes.
不错
Yes, you are.
来吧
Now come on.
你的女儿此刻最需要你
Your girls need you now more than ever.
我不该相信你
I didn't want to believe you.
你告诉我没法治愈
You told me there was no cure,
这些人不是得病  而是已经死掉
That these people were dead, not sick.
我宁愿不去相信这些
I chose not to believe that.
可当我看到肖恩一枪打中卢的胸口
But when shane shot lou in the chest
她还是扑过来的时候
And she just kept coming,
我才知道自己有多傻
That's when I knew what an ass I'd been,
安妮特早就死了
That annette had been dead long ago
我一直在喂养一具腐尸
And I was feeding a rotten corpse!
这我才知道我没有希望
That's when I knew there was no hope.
当那个小女孩走出谷仓时
And when that little girl came out of the barn,
从你脸上的表情
The look on your face--
我就看出你已经知道这点
I knew you knew it too.
对吧
Right?
根本没有希望
There is no hope.
你现在也看得出来吧
And you know it now, like I do.
对不对
Don't you?
我们根本没有任何希望了
There is no hope for any of us.
准备好了吗
You ready?
嗯
Yeah.
这种事  我们究竟还要做多少次
Man, how many times we gonna have to do this?
我受够了  我不会再这样了
Look, I'm done. I'm not doing this anymore,
为你收拾残局
Cleaning up after you.
你想听实话吗
You know what the truth is?
什么事都没有改变
Nothing has changed.
死就是死  人终有一死
Death is death. It's always been there,
无论是死于心脏病 癌症
Whether it's from a heart attack, cancer,
或是成为行尸  有什么区别吗
Or a walker. What's the difference?
之前你可没有这样绝望吧
You didn't think it was hopeless before, did you?
现在家里的人
Now there are people back
在努力活下去  他们需要我们
at home trying to hang on. They need us,
就算是给他们一个活下去的理由也好
Even if it's just to give them a reason to go on,
即便是我们自己也不相信也罢
Even if we don't believe it ourselves.
这已经不是
You know what? This-- this isn't about
我们相不相信的事
What we believe anymore.
而是他们相信与否
It's about them.
真没想到  见到活人了
Son of a bitch. They're alive.
我叫戴夫
I'm dave.
那个皮包骨头的棒槌是托尼
That scrawny-looking douche bag there is tony.
吃我啊（滚蛋）  戴夫
Eat me, dave.
说不定哪天我就吃了你
Hey, maybe someday I will.
我在费城那边的高速上遇到他的
We met on I-95 coming out of philly.
那边的景象好凄惨
Damn shit-show that was.
我叫格伦  很高兴见到一些新面孔
I'm Glenn. It's nice to meet some new people.
瑞克 格兰姆斯
Rick Grimes.
老哥你贵姓
How about you, pal? Have one?
我刚退出了组织
I just quit.
朋友  你可真会选时候
You've got a unique sense of timing, my friend.
他叫赫谢尔
His name's Hershel.
他今天失去很多亲友
He lost people today, a lot of them.
节哀顺便
I'm truly sorry to hear that.
为明天会更好和结交新朋友
To better days and new friends.
以及逝去的亲友
And to our dead--
愿他们永享极乐
May they be in a better place.
不错吧
Not bad, huh?
在一个警察身上拿来的
I got it off a cop.
我就是个警察
I'm a cop.
我说的这个已经死了
This one was already dead.
你们大老远从费城到这里来
You fellas are a long way from philadelphia.
从这里到哪里都很远
It feels like we're a long way from anywhere.
什么促使你到南边来
Well, what drove you south?
肯定不是天气的原因
Well, I can tell you it wasn't the weather.
光是流汗  我就大概减了15斤左右
I must've dropped 30 lbs. In sweat alone down here.
吹牛
I wish.
其实本打算先去华府
No, first it was d.C.
听说那边有难民营
I heard there might be some kind of refugee camp,
结果公路堵塞  我们寸步难行
But the roads were so jammed, we never even got close.
于是决定不走公路  而走乡间
We decided to get off the highways, into the sticks,
一路马不停蹄
Keep hauling ass.
遇到的每一伙人
Every group we came across
都说有逃出升天的办法
had a new rumor about a way out of this thing.
有人说驻扎在海湾的海警
One guy told us there was the coast guard sitting in the gulf,
将渡船发往各个小岛
Sending ferries to the islands.
近期又说蒙哥马利那边有个火车站
The latest was a rail yard in montgomery
那里有火车开往中部地区
Running trains to the middle of the country--
堪萨斯  内布拉斯加等地
Kansas, Nebraska.
内布拉斯加吗
Nebraska?
人口稀少  枪支泛滥
Low population, lots of guns.
这倒是
Kinda makes sense.
去过内布拉斯加吗  小伙
Ever been to nebraska, kid?
把那里称作是穷乡僻壤是有原因的
A reason they call 'em flyover states.
你们呢
How about you guys?
本宁堡
Fort benning, eventually.
警官  我不想打击你
I hate to piss in your cornflakes, officer, but...
我们遇到过几个驻扎在本宁堡的士兵
We ran across a grunt who was stationed at benning.
说那边已被群尸占领
He said the place was overrun by lamebrains.
本宁堡已经失陷了  真的吗
Wait, fort benning is gone? Are you for real?
是的
Sadly, I am.
说实话  这件事没有解决办法
Oddly, the truth is there is no way out of this mess.
只能不断幻想
Just keep going from one pipe dream to the next,
不要被丧失心智的怪物抓住
doesn't grab a hold of you when you sleep.
如果你还能睡着的话
If you sleep.
没错  看起来你们并不住在这里
Yeah, it doesn't look like you guys are hanging your hats here.
你们在有其他藏身处吗
You holed up somewhere else?
没有
Not really.
门口是你们的车吗
Those your cars out front?
是的  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
我们住在车里
We're living in ours.
可你们的车又空又干净
Those look kinda empty, clean.
-你们的行李在哪里  -我们一大队人
- Where's all your gear? - We're with a larger group
出来侦查  顺便喝两杯
out scouting, thought we could use a drink.
喝两杯  赫谢尔  你不是戒酒了吗
A drink? Hershel, I thought you quit.
我们想在这附近扎营
Well, we're thinking of setting up around here.
-这里安全吗  -还算安全
- Is it-- is it safe? - It can be,
尽管我在附近干掉过几只行尸
Although I have killed a couple of walkers around here.
"行尸"  你们这样叫它们
Walkers? That what you call them?
-没错  -挺好
- Yeah. - That's good.
我喜欢  这称呼比"蠢蛋"更好
I like that. I like that better than lamebrains.
更简洁
More succinct.
-好吧  托尼上过大学  -只上了2年
- Okay, Tony went to college. - Two years.
那么  你们是在郊区
So what-- so what, you guys set up
还是别的地方扎营
On the outskirts or something?
-那片新小区  -家庭拖车还是什么
- That new development? - Trailer park or something?
是农场吗
A farm?
*老麦克唐纳有个农场*
*Old McDonald had a farm*
你有农场吗
You got a farm?
-安全吗  -肯定安全
- Is it safe? - It's gotta be.
-有食物和水吗  -有妞吗
- You got food, water? - You got cooze?
我很久没干过女人了
Ain't had a piece of ass in weeks.
听着  原谅我朋友
Listen, pardon my friend.
城里孩子说话冲
City kids-- they got no tact.
他无意冒犯
No disrespect.
-听着  格兰  -我们说的够多了
- So listen, Glenn-- - We've said enough.
等等  这农场听起来不错
Well, hang on a second. This farm-- it sounds pretty sweet.
-听起来是不是很棒  托尼  -没错  非常棒
- Don't it sound sweet, Tony? - Yeah, real sweet.
来点南方人的热情好客如何
How about a little southern hospitality?
我们营地还有兄弟  日子过得挺艰难
We got some buddies back at camp, been having a real hard time.
你为什么不给我们腾点地方呢
I don't see why you can't make room for a few more.
我们可以共享资源和人力
We can pool our resources, our manpower.
很抱歉  这不行
Look, I'm sorry. That's not an option.
听起来没什么问题啊
Doesn't sound like it'd be a problem.
对不起  我们不能那样
I'm sorry. We can't.
我们不能再接收更多人了
We can't take in any more.
你们可跟我想的不一样
You guys are something else.
我以为我们是朋友
I thought-- I thought we were friends.
我们也有人需要照顾
We got people we gotta look out for too.
-我们一点都不了解你们  -没错  你说的对
- We don't know anything about you. - No, that's true.
你一点都不了解我们
You don't know anything about us.
你不知道我们在外面经历过什么
You don't know what we've had to go through out there,
那些我们不得不干的事
The things we've had to do.
我打赌有些事你自己也被迫做过
I bet you've had to do some of those same things yourself.
对吗
Am I right?
在这个世道  没有谁的手是干净的
'cause ain't nobody's hands clean in what's left of this world.
我们都一样
We're all the same.
所以来吧
So come on, let's--
让我们快乐的坐着拖拉机去农场
Let's take a nice friendly hayride to this farm
然后好好认识一下对方
and we'll get to know each other.
那不可能发生
That's not gonna happen.
这简直是胡扯
This is bullshit.
-冷静一下  -别叫我冷静
- Calm down. - Don't tell me to calm down.
永远别对我说冷静
Don't ever tell me to calm down.
我要崩了你们三个混蛋
I'll shoot you three assholes
然后把他妈的农场抢过来
in the head and take your damn farm!
等等  等等  放松
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa. Relax.
别紧张  谁也不会杀谁
Take it easy. Nobody's killing anybody.
谁也不会崩了谁  对吧瑞克
Nobody's shooting anybody. Right, Rick?
看着
Look.
我们只是几个朋友喝一杯  仅此而已
We're just friends having a drink. That's all.
好酒放哪里了
Now where's the good stuff, huh?
好酒  好酒  让我找找
Good stuff, good stuff, good stuff. Let's see.
看看这个
Hey, look at that.
这酒可以
That'll work.
你要明白
You gotta understand--
我们不能待在外面
We can't stay out there.
你知道外面是什么样子
You know what it's like.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I do.
但农场现在太拥挤了
But the farm is too crowded as is.
抱歉  但你必须继续找
I'm sorry. You'll have to keep looking.
继续寻找
Keep looking.
你觉得我该去哪里找
Where do you suggest we do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我听说内布拉斯加州不错
I hear Nebraska's nice.
内布拉斯加州
Nebraska.
你啊...
This guy...